Woke up quick and at about noon Just thought that I had to be incompetent soon I gotta get drunk before the day begins For a month to start bitchin' bout my plants Bout to go a damn year with blind new fellas at the bathroom Went up both sides, ran in the house and grabbed a clip At the back, 10 on the side of my hip Failed outside and boarded my weapon Just about to pull the gat step in Jump in the boy, hit the juice, I'm alive I got brought back and then side to side Then I went down by play, play Bumpin' new shit, buyin' me away It was gangsta gangsta, the top of the list And I played my own shit with someone like this Who's down the street?
Him, my six-hole chuckin' the bitches Slappin' the hoes, went to the park to get the stew Knock all hens out of the cove
Shootin' some hoops, Scott pulls up with K to B A fresh up for me, a rollin' Q to D Both at his window, he's talkin' the same It's all about makin' mad GTA Cause the boys in the hood are on his heart You come talkin' that trash, we'll pull your car
Knowin' how it ain't like, but to be a chick The punky boy, cuz I ain't sick, shit Florida's hell, I don't wanna get ill So I went to a spot where my homeboys chill The fellas that's out there makin' that dollar I pull up at the month's six, don't know how I pay pre with a forty and I start pregnant with an eight Call my best boss, toss to the left To get big girl that I find by eatin' from the left I hit that fat girl and eat the house Get out of the paddo, said that maniac that she said Something that I couldn't believe, so I grabbed this scumbag bitch with a grabby ass weed She start shit, who knows, just like a man Slap the hoe, where her heart jumps up and she's supposed to just shout
It's a door I cross and I've just knocked his old ass out.
Cause the boys in the hood are always hard.
Er, you can't come in and trash, for you're poor, you're caught.
Knowing that it ain't life, but to be legit Don't pull me, boy, cause I ain't said shit I'm low and hard, now under control, then wrap the six around the telephone pole I looked in my car and I said, no, brother, I pulled in the gutter and go I'm buying another walkin' home and I see a G-Ride, no Cadiz Tryin' to chew on the side, fake bust a U-Bit, got pulled over Undercover top and a dog ring, no love Cat beat, folded his hips, and the rest of his socks are peekin' and hit the road And this guest now, gee, is tough, but doin' the crime Pull the fence on the boy, he'll do some time For a finesse
Yeah, yeah